Historical facts
that will distort
your perception of time.
The cowboy era
and the Victorian era
took place at the same time.
Machu picchu and the Sistine Chapel
were built just 33 years apart
Abraham Lincoln
and the samurai era
took place at the same time.
There were still woolly mammoths
roaming the earth
when the great pyramids
were under construction.
Cleopatra was alive closer in time
to us today than she was
to the pyramids construction.
The City of London is
1,500 years older than Genghis Khan.
The Ottoman empire was
still around when Walt Disney
released his first cartoons.
The eastern Roman empire
fell just 39 years before Columbus
discovered the Americas.
Saturns rings did not even exist
when the stegosaurus
was roaming the earth.