Mi  Wu, this can of coke for you
It has no pull tab
oh I didn't noticed,
can you still open it?
Think it has no pull tap
Well,
the opening of the can is very thin.
I just need to keep some distance
and repeatedly rub the opening with a pen.
So as to..
don't just drink.
Have some jelly.
You also got jelly.
um? Where are the edges gone?
absolutely not!
you know me.
I got an idea,
wipe the bottom and
give it a gentle bite.
hey snacks are unhealthy
drink coconut water.
Wow You even got a coconut for me.
well Do you have a knife on you?
Why would I keep a knife with me?
I've got chopsticks
chopsticks.
How can I make it?
Let's see how you handle this.
oh I got an idea.
There is a soft spot
on the top of the coconut.
that serves as a nutrient transfer point.
So all you need to do is poke it in the center
and then explore around the area.
You really think
you can open a coconut with the chopstick?
are't you a nice person?