You want to keep
the small blueberries
throw away the big ones,
keep the big raspberries,
throw away the small ones,
take the small blueberry,
squeeze it
into the big raspberry.
And then you want to freeze these.
Once frozen, you're
going to melt
some white chocolate
over a dull boiler.
Until nice and smooth,
then you take
your frozen raspberry.
chuck it into the white chocolate
coat it all over.
With the fork,
shake off the excess,
put it back in the freezer,
freeze it up again.
And now you take
some dark chocolate
or some milky chocolate
and coat it again,
shake off the excess.
and There you go
back in the freezer
and you got this amazing,
little frozen fruit treat for summer.