Tom Cruise closes out the Paris olympics in an epic way.
At the closing ceremony for the 2024 olympics,
the mission impossible star,
who's known to do his own stunts,
goes full action hero mode and completes the craziest routine ever.
He starts out by repelling from the Top of the stage to France
down to the stage where he grabs the olympic flag from
Simone Biles and the Los Angeles Mayor Karen bass.
To head back to the us Tom then jumps on his motorcycle and rides
off into the night with the olympic flag waving on the back.
But his antics didn't stop there.
The actor then catches a flight in skydives back to California where he's
seen parachuting down to the Hollywood sign,
leading the way for epic performance.
From Billy Irish,
the Red Hot Chili Peppers,
snoop dog and more.