11 things,
people learn
too late in life.
One,
the less you say,
the more your words
will matter.
Two,
don't take
everything personally,
not everyone
thinks about you
as much as you do.
Three,
when you focus on problems,
you have more problems.
When you focus on possibilities,
you'll have more opportunities.
Four,
no matter how much
it hurts now,
someday you will look back and realize
your struggle changed your life
for the better
five.
You meet people for a reason.
Either you need
them to change your life
or you're the one
that will change theirs,
six.
Never be afraid to try something new.
Life gets boring when you stay
within the limits
of what you already know.
Seven.
You will never truly know
the value of a moment
until it becomes a memory
Eight.
Once you
begin to take note
of the things you
are grateful for,
you begin to lose sight
of the things that you lack.
Nine,
if you do not have control
over your mouth,
you do not have control
over your future.
Ten.
life is a mirror
and will reflect back to the thinker
what he thinks in.