Why are you late?
yeah I remember
when you told me
yesterday that the bell
does not dismiss you,
I dismiss you.
yeah What about it?
well If the bell
does not dismiss me,
it does not tell
me when to get
here on time.
Get out of my class, Ryan.
Why?
Because I was 5 minutes late,
you weren't even in class yesterday.
I know, but that's not important.
yeah it is It's way
more important for you
to be here than us.
The substitute
gave you
homework yesterday,
put on my desk
on your way out,
finished it in class yesterday.
I put it on your desk,
Ryan. Why are your answers
from question one?
All the way to question 8
exactly the same as Michael's answers?
oh I don't know,
maybe because we
were answering
the same questions.
Can you believe this?
oh By the way,
toss me pencil?
hey No, talking
to each other
during class.
Why are you teaching
during my conversation?
That's it.
To the principal's office?
Now?
Fine. Can I go
to the bathroom
on the way?
What for ...
to open the chamber of secrets?!!!
What do you think?
Out!!!