It's taken me
500 years to learn
these little planting tricks.
For corn,
put it in a container,
cover with water,
and wait for it
to sprout,
then plant it
in the soil and water it.
You can now grow
your own corn
at home
for tomatoes,
sliced store,
bought ones
and lay them
flat in nutrient rich soil,
cover them
with another layer,
water them regularly
and wait for them
to sprout.
This way you
won't have to buy
tomatoes anymore.
For roses split
a branch
in the middle, insert,
a piece of chewing gum,
cut a piece of banana,
wrap it around the gum,
secure it with a tie
and cover it
with a plastic cup.
Add some soil,
moistened with water
and roots will form
at the wound,
cut it off,
transplant it into a pot
and you've got
a new rose bush
for green beans,
put them in a bottle
with water.
Shake, well,
punch seven holes
in the cap,
drain the water
and let it sit
soon,
the beans will sprout.
How would you rate them
out of ten?!!