The funny thing
about this joke
is that the more time passes,
the better it gets.
Did you hear
the story
about the kid
who was
outside the democratic fundraiser
selling kittens?!!
When the people
came out from the fundraiser,
he was holding up the kittens.
And he was saying
buy a democrat kitten,
well ... a couple
of weeks later,
the republicans
held a fundraiser
in the same place.
and When they came out,
there was
the same kid
with the kittens.
And he said
buy a republican kitten
and one of the members
of the press
who had seen him
there 2 weeks before,
said,
"wait a minute" kid.
You were selling
these kittens
the last time
as democrat kittens.
How come
they are republican kittens now?
kid says,
"because now they
got their eyes open."