I'm making some really
great progress
this week on what is
one of my biggest
and definitely my most ambitious
mold project to date.
It's pretty normal mold
at first two parts,
fill it,
pour it out,
cut the extra off.
But then this design
takes a little turn.
You add
these internal supports
that go under the foot
and hold up the Top.
Another mold part
is added to the bottom,
pop it out of the mold.
And the other new part
is injecting slip
through the Top that cast
the last part
of the bottom seamlessly,
and we end up
with a fully enclosed form.
From there,
i'll add whatever glaze
finishing effects that I
decide I want on it.
In this case,
it's dragon's blood.
So green under glaze biscuit,
dip it in the grape jelly,
the other side glaze fire.
Here we go
the finish piece.
but Unfortunately,
it's not quite there yet.