This is by far the most difficult
and detailed cake
that i've ever made.
So a lot of you
wanted to see me
make SpongeBob.
And I was a little hesitant
to do this one,
because I knew how complicated
it would be,
but I was
up for the Challenge.
So I sacked the cake up.
I covered that with chocolate garnish,
and then I'm
going to decorate this cake,
use a modeling chocolate.
And the hardest thing
about this is that I'm turning
a 2-D character into a 3-D cake.
And that's a really difficult thing
to do.
So I have to look at so many pictures
of SpongeBob
from all different size
just to make
sure that I had
all the proportions.
Great.
And once I
finished
with his facial features,
I still had
other things
to model
like his legs,
his shoes,
and also his arms,
which I held
into place using
wire.
And now some add
color
to this cake.
And I'm doing this
by using
a combination
of both edible paint and air brushing,
because I
wanted to add
as much detail
to this cake
that I possibly could.
And this is
the part that
is really fun,
but it is difficult.
I'm just trying to make
sure that I
don't miss
anything up
at this point.
And I finished
all the last details by using
different colored modeling chocolate
to make his teeth,
his tie in his eyelashes,
and that makes
this SpongeBob cake Complete.
I'm sponge Bob.