Most people
don't understand
how deep the ocean really is.
Imagine you walk off the coast
into the water at 10 meters
or 33 feet deep,
you're already experiencing
an entire additional atmosphere
of pressure
at 214 meters. You're passing
the verified record for a human diver
with no equipment.
At 830, you're the depth
of the tallest building on earth
and 1,000 meters down.
No light from the surface
is getting to you anymore.
And you're only about 1/10
of the way down,
1220 meters.
And you're
in the territory of the deepest
military submarines that we know about
at 3800 meters,
you hit the Titanic.
And just above it is where the infamous
ocean gate submersible imploded.
The deepest recorded natural point is
10,984 meters deep or 6.8 miles.
You might have heard of this point.
This is challenger deep.
If you put Mount Everest
into the water upside down
there would still be over a Mile
until you got to the bottom.
The ocean is just amazing.
But the thing is we haven't
mapped it very well.
If you want to know more
about the crazy effort
to map our oceans,
watch this video
over here.