Making the paper disappear.
This is gonna be hard, man.
I don't know
how they're gonna match
like the little,
like the shine on the orange,
you see like throughout the
whole oranges
like these little shines of light,
I think that's impossible to match.
So far I could do this. Okay?
That's what I'm gonna
say right now.
I could do what they've done up
until this point.
Right here is probably where they
lose my skill level.
uh No, so far so good.
okay yeah This is where we lose
my skill level.
They are doing the shine.
Look at it .. slowly, but surely
this is so satisfying.
Why is it so peaceful?!!
I could watch this for hours.
It just feels so peaceful.
i got to see the shine ... man,
oh there they go,
they add the shine,
oh it looks so good.
I feel like you can still see
like the the crust .. the peel
the peel, that's it.
I saw I feel you could tell
at the peel.