Apple has just announced
the new iPhone 16,
and here's what's new
first colors, along with the usual
white and black leather, teal,
aquamarine and a pink option,
adding a pop of color
to the regular iPhone range.
Also get
a tougher ceramic shield glass
on the display.
The display can reach
up to 2,000 nits
in bright daylight
to go as dim as one nit,
but sadly,
no 120 hertz.
Promotion goodness.
Yet, in this basic model,
the action button
has been added
from last year's 15 PRO,
giving you a shortcut key
for different
programmable functions.
And there's a new button
on the side
called the camera control.
It's pressure and touch sensitive.
So it can tell
when you're
pressing it
firmly or softly and can be used
to snap photos
or control focus,
zoom depth of field
or even switch between
different photographic styles
inside. There's a new a18
processor for really fast,
powerful performance
and the ability
to run triple a games.
And apple Intelligence
plus the battery is much
bigger this time, too,
as for cameras
as a new primary 48 megapixels
so fusion camera
alongside a 12 mega pixel,
ultra wide camera
with auto focus
for macro ability.
So what do you think?