The phone with a unique form factor,
rich de Miro takes a look at Samsung latest foldable phone.
After Samsung launch event in Paris,
I spent the day with their entry level foldable phone, the flip six.
This year's model has an upgraded look and feel less of a visible screen crease,
and the cameras got a big quality boost.
The main advantage of a flip style phone is that you can use
the main cameras for a majority of shots including selfish.
Samsung calls this flex mode,
Samsung flex mode lets you leave the phone half open to give you
more versatile capture options.
A feature called auto frame uses AI to hone in on a subject.
It's not always perfect right now we are going for a traditional French lunch.
As you can see, the streets here are very crowded.