The trap that most people fall for is when they speak,
they get stuck
in a default rate of speech.
I'll be dramatic here.
I get stuck at a two watch what happens to your brains automatically.
If I just, hi, everyone,
it's great to be here.
You start to feel a pain.
so If you get stuck in a slow default rate of speech,
not influential,
nor is it impact full.
But then again,
I used to do this because I'm part Vietnamese,
and I speak really quickly.
I'm really good to be here.
Can't wait to take you through vocal foundation.
It's going to be amazing.
You're thinking,
do Asian and south Australians breathe?
Really interesting now,
because if we go to about a six,
hi,  everyone really excited to be here to take you
through the vocal foundations
for the next couple of days.
And as we learned the vocal foundations,
what you start to realize in your own head
is what starts started out
as being really engaging
after a while
becomes monotonous.
Isn't that weird?
Because then you're thinking
well what the Frick do I do.
Then this is where you learn the importance of variety.
Vocal variety is key.