Have you ever wondered
what the worst year to be alive was?
well According to historians,
it's the year 536
during a time called the dark ages.
Here's what happened
and how things just kept getting worse.
In 536,
a massive volcano erupted in Iceland.
This resulted in heavy smoke,
blocking the sun,
creating constant darkness for 18 months.
But that's just the start.
The darkness LED to global temperatures severely dropping,
and because of this crops and irrigation completely fake,
leading to mass starvation.
But here's the worst part.
After a few years of this,
the justinian plague hit and spread all across Europe.
The plague wipe down up to 50 million people,
which at the time was roughly half the world's population,
making it the worst year to be alive.