Study people who eat a diet high in fruits and vegetables could reduce
the risk of heart and kidney disease.
Researchers took more than 150 people with high blood pressure who were
at risk for kidney disease and divided them into 3 groups.
1 group added 2 to 4 cups of fruits and veggies to their diet.
Each day, another added two daily doses of baking soda,
and one continued with standard medical care.
The study found that after 5 years,
the first two diets promoted kidney health,
but the fruit and vegetable diet improved heart health as well.
The american Heart Association recommends 4 to 5 servings of fruits and vegetables a day