Unbelievable.
The inventor
of the RAM air turbine
is truly a genius.
This device
only appears
when an aircraft
encounters
an emergency.
The R8 consists
of 2 to 4 or 6 to 10 medium
length blades resembling
a ship's propeller.
When both
the main engines
and auxiliary power systems
fail,
the R8
becomes
the aircraft's
last lifeline.
It automatically deploys
from the bottom
of the plane
using the airflow
generated during the planes
glide to spin and produce
electricity and hydraulic power.
The faster the plane speed,
the greater the R8s output
power.
The R8s blades
can spin at a rate
of 5,000 to 7,000 revolutions
per minute,
providing 5 to 70 kilovar
of power
and hydraulic power
for the landing gear
system.
Although it
only produces
1/18 of the power
of a regular generator.