It starts off on an ocean slice where a young lady is using
her island laptop on the beach.
Each key is a different music genre.
My favorite is the lo fi island where you drink winter themed hot chocolate.
In one cup.
A woman sits with her morning coffee on her phone is a nice view from space.
It takes a minute,
but if you zoom far enough,
you'll find a dorm room in that room.
You'll find the setting for one of my web comics about a smartphone that
came to life and trapped four heroes.
You can see them hanging out on one of the APP islands,
looking up at the moon in the distance where another story is unfolding.
This time set on a train where each car is a different biome.
My favorite is the autumn cafe car.
It has pretty good WiFi,
so you can make calls or watch videos on your phone.
Like this, one about a minecraft server centered around a holy rubis cube.
On one of the tropical sites.
I built a house.
Here you could find me working on this weird drawing idea.
I had about an ocean slice.
This is the biggest drawing i've ever made.