I can't find my daughter
Selina, she's dressed like stitch
oh ma'am,
she's
she's right over there.
No,
there were two kids dressed as Stitch.
okay.
A parent probably just grabbed the wrong kid.
Okay,
did your mom or dad accidentally leave without yo, Alton？
my dad.
okay and what's your dad's name?
Daddy.
okay I got this.
Do you know where you live?
oh Great.
You are so smart.
Where?
in the house.
MHM yeah okay police.
would I lie to you?
Invest now, buddy
get in on the ground floor and i'll make you rich.
What? I'm busy.
sir,
you're the prime suspect in the kidnapping.
Did you just take a child from the Midwest police station?
yeah My son, Alton.
sir, that is not your son.
Hey,
could you take off your hood, please?
Hi.
holy crap.
I swear, I had no idea.
more candy.
You can ask your mom.
Let's go.
No,
I want to stay here.
My mom doesn't let me eat sugar.