When I was a kid,
I said,
if you dug a hole
from the United States
where would you come out
on the other side?
And all everyone says,
dig a hole
all the way
to China,
right?!
That's always the case.
However,
China is not where you
will land.
If you dig a hole
through the center
of the earth,
because if you dig
a hole through the center
and you start
in the northern hemisphere,
you have to end
up in the southern hemisphere.
If you start
in the western hemisphere,
you gotta end up
in the eastern hemisphere.
That's how
the geometry works.
Exactly!! Because it's a ball
it's a ball.
Right?
All right?
so when I did
the measurements on that,
if you dug that hole
from the United States
you would end up
in the Indian Ocean
You just fled
the United States
all the water would
come through,
you pop through,
and also you like,
oh lord,
what have I done?