What if the moon collided with earth?
And would it cause the death of everyone？
click the subscribe button
and let's find out
the moon helps maintain earth's gravitational pull.
and because of the moon,
earth's gravity stays balanced.
The moon is 30084,000 kilometers away from earth.
This might sound like a lot.
But if the moon started moving towards earth at a rate of 5,000 kilometersper day,
it would reach us in just 75 days
as the moon begins to approach earth，
Earth's gravity will start to weaken
when the moon is about 200,000 kilometers away,
the ocean tides will rise dramatically.
Leading to tsunamis all around the world.
And countries located below sea level will start to flood
as the moon gets even closer to earth.
We will start to experience daily earthquakes and volcanic eruptions.
When the moon is only 6,000 kilometers away from earth,
our atmosphere will tear the moon into thousands of pieces,
which will then begin to orbit around earth.
This event would result in the death of most people on earth.