Why do all the airplanes
in the world
avoid flying
over this zone?
This zone is
quite huge more than 5 times
the size of France.
And if we look
at a flight radar,
we can see
an extensive area
empty of airplanes.
This is the Tibetan plateau.
There are
three main reasons
why planes do not fly here.
Firstly,
Tibet is the highest plateau
in the world
with an average elevation
of about 14,800 feet.
It is home to some
of the highest mountains
on the planet,
including Mount Everest,
commercial aircraft
have to fly
at an altitude
of about 33,000 feet,
but in case
of an emergency
such as a cabin depressurization,
they need to quickly descend
to 10,000 feet
which is almost impossible in Tibet
because of its height.
Secondly,
the weather conditions in Tibet
are often extremely unpredictable,
strong winds,
turbulence and sudden weather changes
make flying over this region
dangerous and challenging.
Finally,
the third reason
is the lack
of sufficient airports
for emergency landings
in the area.
There are
only five airports
in Tibet making flights
over this region extremely risky.