Good morning.
Here's what apple
just announced.
There's a new
Apple Watch series 10
that has
a larger display
is thinner and lets you
play media
directly from a watch
It's now dive certified
and charges
much faster things
to a larger charging coil
oh!!
and it can detect
sleep apnea.
There's the AirPod 4
and the AirPod 4
with noise canceling.
They have a lot
of the same features
that the old AirPod Pros have,
but in a smaller case,
and with 30 hours
of battery life,
oh!! and they
also support
the Apple Watch charger
the AirPod Max is
now have USB C
and just some new colors.
That's about it.
The AirPod Pro 2s
are getting
a huge update
that allow them
to better protect
your ears,
test your ears
and also act
as a hearing aid.
The 16 now has
a camera control button
with a different camera
layout.
For spatial video.
The 16 Pro has
the smallest bezels
on an iPhone,
and the max model
has the largest display yet
they announced
the popo edition,
the a 18 PRO chip,
and it also has
4 studio microphones
to capture
better spatial audio oh
and the wireless charging
just got
that much faster with G2