Have you ever seen your cat wiggle before bouncing?
It's a common sight among cats,
especially when they're preparing to chase after a toy or hunt prey.
Even if it's just a playful interaction with the toy,
First, they do it to check balance or traction.
Cats need to make sure they have a good grip on the ground before they jump.
Just like when runners get ready to sprint.
Cats need to feel steady before they make their move.
The wiggle helps them feel confident
that they won't slip or fall when they leap.
Second, over excitement.
Before they pounce,
cats get really excited.
It's like when you're about to do something super fun.
And you can't wait any longer.
The wiggle is their way of showing that they're pumped up and ready to go.
It's like a signal that says,
I'm so excited. Let's do this.
Take note that the wiggle before a pounce
is different than a cat rubbing its bottom after pooping.
Just like this smart cat right here,
The wiggle is instinctual
while rubbing the bottom is simply because the cat feels uncomfortable.
And when I annoy you by making your bed sheet of tissue paper.