Today I'm flying to Iceland
to find some ice
because my pet Freddie melted.
So I hopped on the plane
and flew across the globe,
but I don't see a single cube
of ice here.
They honestly should have called
this place milk land,
because all I see
is a bunch
of milk,
but but I wasn't
ready to give
up.
I searched
high and found
a secret crater
in the mountains,
and I searched
low and found
some barrels
in a cave.
But where are they
hiding the ice?
I found rocks,
a couple of waterfalls,
some funky buildings,
and even the world's largest flush
button,
but not a single cube
of ice until I
stumbled
upon this doctor
do finish
looking building
and you
wouldn't believe
it.
I found
some ice caves inside,
but where does
this cave go?
What's at the end
of the tunnel?
Ice cream?