I visited Harvard to check out the hardest math class
in the country,
math 55.
Apparently,
this class is so hard that half the students drop out
after the first semester.
And homework assignments can take up to 60 hours a week.
As soon as I sat down,
the professor started throwing up hieroglyphics
on the board.
He was really passionate
and I enjoyed listening to him,
but I wish I knew what he was talking about.
of course the students around me had no problem.
These were twenty to thirty of the most brilliant math students
in the country
being science,
fair winners
and Olympiad medalists.
They were nailing down every single question
the professor asked and even the ones that I asked.