This is the density nine,
and you know
something's luxurious
whenever you get in.
And it sounds like this.
I get a 50 watt
wireless charging PAD,
and I can close
the door using
this screen.
My headrests
are also adjustable.
My seats are heated,
ventilated,
and massaging.
I get a screen here,
another one there.
And if I wanna
video chat somebody,
I just push this.
Have storage space here.
And a cooler right
in there.
I can also heat
this area to keep
my food nice and warm.
And if I need
a place to eat it,
I have a built in table,
a built in cup holder.
And if I don't want glare
on this screen,
I have a built-in sunscreen shade.
I can also fully recline
here in the back.
And if I want to take
a nap,
I can do this
Guan zheyang ying.
yes?
I get wood
here on my dash.
I got
a touch screen
that works super fast.
I have
a wireless charging PAD,
this gorgeous shifter.
and I have fragrances
that blow out of the vents.
I also get a head
up display
a digital display
and built-in karaoke.