Everyone nowadays believes in education,
we train kids to do maths,
we teach pilots how to land planes and surgeons,
how to operate on our brains.
But there's one area where we don't seem to believe in education.
At all, we just leave people to figure out themselves life itself.
There's an odd silence in education when it comes to the truly big questions,
who should we get together with?
How can you manage a relationship?
What career are you suited to?
What's money for?
How can we manage anxiety?
And what do we do with regret and shame?
What do we do about illness and aging?
How do we deal with our families?
Here there is very strangely often no one to turn to nowhere to go.
So stress accumulates and disasters occur.