Things we all did as kids
Using a mechanical pencil to do this
because we thought it was edgy.
Trying to balance the light switch between on and off,
and then our parents would get mad.
Doing this yoga pose and seeing who could hold it the longest,
whatever the heck this is called,
maybe counter uppies.
Draw the special "s"
Try to catch the refrigerator light turning off
Poke the eraser with our pencil over and over and over again, showing no mercy
Stocking all of our fingers on top of each other
Ice skating with socks and pretending that we were an olympic champion.
I got the gold medal every time
Using a paper roll as a megaphone,
Using the electrical box as the meet up spot or the safe spot,
My personal favorite drinking Capri Sun and then doing this.