haw many languages.
Do you speak?
I don't know.
3.
That's what
the word
of a German,
French,
and English.
And I fake Italian,
and you fake Italian.
What's the best?
But if I wanted
to fake French,
like...
that that's
that's a hard one,
right?
Isn't it?
unfakeable
I understand it
more than I can...
Yeah,
when I go there,
I can...
I speak it more than
I understand.
Also,
French people are,
they
they're not flattered
by an attempt
to speak French.
They actually hate
you more,
they hate you more
sometimes for good reason.
But the the Italians
love it.
yes If you stumble,
you wave,
ah they they love it,
let they come
for the water.
They love it.
They got,
at least he try.
ah ... Whereas in France,
they're like,
no,
they do they do.
They do this.
yeah
And especially in Paris,
and and I thought
last time I went
to Paris,
someone did that.
I thought
next time he does it,
i'll break his finger off.