In this video,
I'm gonna make an obsidian knife
for my friend,
because he wants to use it
to fillet a fish.
This big piece I broke off will be
perfect for our blade.
To get started on the blade.
I use a moose antler
to break off big pieces,
thin it down, and also shape it.
I make sure to strike
the obsidian in the right areas
with the correct amount of force.
Otherwise,
I could risk breaking it in half.
and While I
don't usually wear gloves
in my videos,
I'm wearing one in this one
because this stone was so big.
It's also important that I'm
protecting my leg
with leather pads
during this process.
We're getting closer
to the finished blade.
So now I'm using
smaller tools
to sharpen and shape
the blade further.
To finish the blade,
I use deer antler to sharpen it,
as well as create
the tang for it to fit
properly in our antler handle.
The tang in the blade
also allows me to wrap it
securely to the handle
with deer sinew.
I made sure to make
this knife thin and really sharp,
so it'll work well to fillet a fish.