I'm not a young guy.
That's no secret, but here's the deal.
I understand how to get things done for the American people.
I LED the country through the covert crisis.
Today, We have the strongest economy in the world.
I passed the law that lowers prescription of drug prices,
cap sense of the $35 a month for seniors.
For 4 years, Donald Trump tried to pass an infrastructure law and he failed.
I got it done.
Now we're rebuilding America.
I passed the biggest law in history to combat climate change,
because our future depends on it.
Donald trump took away the freedom of women to choose.
I'm determined to make ROE v. wade, the law of the land again.
Donald trump believes the job of the president is to take care of Donald Trump.
I believe the job of the president is to fight for you,
the American people,
and that's what I'm doing.
I'm Joe Biden and I approve this message.