This girl is the world's best makeup artists in the world.
And you can easily see why every single time she puts on makeup,
she creates an absolutely insane illusion.
So you can't even tell which part is real or fake
Like in this one, it looks like she has 2 pairs of eyes.
But in the very next one,
it looks like her entire face is made out of glass.
And although these ones are mind blowing,
you won't believe how good number 16 is.
But this one makes it look like her entire face is just one giant mouth,
and you can't even tell until she opens her eyes.
So that just shows how good her skills really are.
But the amount of practice she needed to do these must have been a ton
since only a PRO would be able to do it like she does.
But while some of them are like an optical illusion,
others are just really good positioning and lighting.
But this one makes it look like her face is gone,
and some of them make it look like her eyes are facing the entirely wrong direction
while she can also make it looks like two faces somehow bleached together.
But if you guys thought this was cool, go follow her insta.