Have you ever wondered
how massive oil rigs
are constructed in the middle
of the deep ocean?
well .. The ocean's depth
is pretty staggering.
The deepest point ever recorded
by humans is 6.8 miles.
If you put Mount Everest
up upside down in the ocean
there would still be over a Mile
until you get to the bottom.
so How is it possible to build
these mega structures
in the midst of all this
where waves can be
as tall as a 10-story building?
Some people even jokingly say
that they build the oil rigs
first and then build the ocean
around them.
You see,
in shallow waters,
fixed steel structures
are installed in the ocean floor,
but for the deeper waters,
floating platforms are used that
are anchored
securely to the ocean floor.