A woman saw
three men standing
outside her home,
she approached
them and asked,
are you hungry?
Would you like to come inside?
One of the men asked is
your husband home?
She replied, no,
he isn't home yet.
they said then we
cannot enter
when her husband returned.
She told him
about the men.
He said "go and invite them in"
She invited them,
but they said we
cannot all come in together.
The woman asked why not
the first man smiled and said
I am wealth.
The second said I am success,
and the third said I am love.
Wealth continued.
Go ask your husband
which one of us he
wants to invite
the woman returned
and relayed their words
after thinking.
The husband said,
"let's invite wealth"
The wife suggested
"maybe we should invite success,"
then their child spoke up,
"let's invite love, then our home will be
full of happiness"
touched by his words,
the parents agreed
the woman went
back and said "we
have decided to invite love"
to her surprise
as love walked toward their house,
wealth and success followed.
The woman asked "I only invited love
Why are you both coming?"
One of the men replied
"wherever love goes,
wealth and success follow"