And what's your name?
Maggie.
I'm sorry.
Why are you answering for her?
And he doesn't talk yet
Maggie, we can't take a non-talker.
Okay What's a good side dish?
Rice.
Why not caviar?
Oh my god You're not just smart.
You're brilliant.
Well look, who's back
Just because Maggie can't talk
Doesn't mean she's dumb.
Fine.
I'll give her an IQ test.
How many eyes do you have?
Well congratulations.
You're now as intelligent as a pig.
Let's see if you can move up to dolphin.
How many people in your family?
oh I got that one, right, too.
Maggie Simpson, IQ 167.
My IQ is only 159.
Maggie is more intelligent than me.
Our kids keep getting smarter.
If we have another one.
It could build a time machine which we could use to go back in time and not have any kids.