The girl gave her boyfriend
a cute little fox
as a birthday gift
little did she know?
It would turn
out to be one
of the biggest mistakes
of her life,
the Fox's cuteness
quickly won
the boy's heart.
bought iyLots of adorable toys
and spent hours playing,
hide and seek with it.
The fox, in turn,
loved its owner deeply.
Every day it
patiently waited
by the window
for him to come
home and then eagerly ran
into his arms for cuddles.
At night,
it would excitedly jump
onto the man's bed
wanting to be held
while they slept together.
However, the girlfriend's arrival
disrupted this harmony,
the fox became very
anxious and resistant.
Every morning it
would either hide
under the covers,
moody or spend the night
howling, non stop.
Frustrated man had
no choice,
but to separate
from his girlfriend and sleep
with the fox.
Instead,
the fox
finally showed
a happy smile
and only then did
the man realize
how much the fox
truly cared for him !!!