Remember who invented
the airplane?!!
well this guy didn't,
but he's going to
build one, too.
An amphibious plane
made of recycled materials.
The first thing he
had to do was build
the base
with water bottles
filled with foam.
He made
a perfect floating base
and added some wheels.
Then he took one
of those plastic barrels
and cut it in half.
He screwed metal pipes
to these plastic sheets,
creating the body
of his plane.
He added the propeller
in the front.
He also screwed
on a comfortable seat
in a windshield.
With PVC pipes,
softened with heat,
the man was
able to make the wings
of his plane.
He painted them
and with his vehicle
on the beach,
he asked his friends
for help
to finish assembling
all the pieces.
There was enough wind
that day for the plane
to move through the sand,
straight into the water.
What do you think?
Could this guy
in his plane go
down in history?
If you're
inspired to build
your own flying machine,
share your ideas
with us?