Have you ever noticed that earth appears ..
to be dripping
like almost every glob of land ..
tapers off in the same direction ..
like all of its melting and running down south ..
to pool at the bottom
well .. a lot of people have,
it's called continental drip
and it's real.
Lee just a coincidence.
We just happen to be alive.
When earth happens to look like this.
Our brains have a tendency to find
meaningful connections ..
in unrelated things.
It's called "apothenia",
but when it involves images and sounds,
it's called "paradigm".
It's how we notice that Italy looks like a boot.
The Nile looks like Vietnam,
Namibia, and Zimbabwe,
look like the creation of Adam.
The Americas look like a duck.
Finland looks like a waving woman.
Australia looks like cat dog.
And even though it actually broke from Antarctica
a 100 million years ago,
somehow also fits into the east coast of the USA.
It's also why we can rearrange
earth's land masses to look like a mouse
or a cow ..... or a chicken,
even a fire, breathing, t-rex.