ah Hey, babe.
Work's been a mess.
Just can't wait to sit down
and do absolutely nothing.
WOW!!
Thank you.
ok do you have to shower
like, what do you have to do
I mean that all
depends on what
you want.
No,
we're not doing
that right now.
We have to go.
oh Yes,
we have to go
where?
you forgot.
I forgot.
I wasn't call you.
I wasn't remind you,
but I thought no ...
there's no way
you're going to forget.
There's no way
look at your face.
of course I didn't forget.
I got my suit pressed.
I got us a bottle of wine,
I put money in the card.
Are you ready?
Do you have
your shoes on?
Are you ready at the car?
Don't do that story.
okay Okay.
You look fantastic.
Thank you.
I can't wait to hear
your speech tonight.
Meet me in the car.