This girl
is the world's best
makeup artists
in the world.
And you
can easily see why
every single time
she puts on makeup,
she creates an absolutely
insane illusion.
So you
can't even tell
which part is
real or fake
like in this one.
it looks like she has
2 pairs of eyes.
But in the very next one,
it looks like
her entire face
is made out of glass.
And although these ones
are mind blowing,
you won't believe
how good number 16 is,
but this one
makes it look
like her entire face is
just one giant mouth,
and you
can't even tell
until she opens
her eyes.
So that just shows
how good her
skills really are.
But the amount
of practice she
needed to do these
must have been
a ton
since only a professional
would be
able to do it
like she does.
But while some
of them are
like an optical illusion,
others are
just really good positioning
and lighting.
But this one
makes it look
like her face
is gone,
and some of them
make it look
like her eyes are facing
the entirely wrong direction
she can also make it
look like two faces
somehow glitch together.
But if you guys
thought this was cool,
go follow her insta.