The ten most reliable
vehicles of the year,
according to Consumer Reports.
I don't think anyone's
gonna be really surprised
by this list,
but it is
worth noting
that Consumer Reports
only surveys its subscribers
and This year,
their data is based
on more than 330,000 vehicles
as reported
by their owners.
Scored from 1 to 100
with 100 being the best.
Starting with number 10,
we have
the Toyota Highlander hybrid
scored at 75.
Number nine,
the corolla
with a score
of 77 followed
by the Acura RDX number 8
scored at 80.
The Toyota RAV4
also comes in
with a score of 80
putting it at 7th place.
Next we've got
the Subaru forester
at number 6
with the score of 82,
and the BMW X5
takes 5th also
with a score of 82.
Number 4 is
the Toyota RAV4 prime
scored at 84,
followed by the number 3
Toyota Camry
with a score of 86.
Number 2 is
the Camry hybrid
with a score of 87,
and last but not least
the most reliable vehicle,
according to Consumer Reports.
The Toyota 4Runner
also with a score
of 87.