Who said dogs are loyal
and cats are selfish.
Cats are your hero in five ways.
One,
if you take your cat
for a walk and it
suddenly becomes aggressive,
don't hesitate, just run.
A girl in China stopped her
evening stroll because
her cat kept hissing.
It turned out that two murders happened
in the that location that day,
cats can hear the footsteps
of predator from hundreds
of meters away and cats let
their owners know about danger
by showing alert,
two.
If your cat suddenly try searching
for a hiding spot or even arching
its back at nothing,
quickly take your cat
to a safe place.
Cats often exhibit these behaviors
about 10 to 30 minutes
before an earthquake occurs.
And that has saved
many cat owners.
Three,
if your cat starts being more cleaning and
protective towards the female owner
like not allowing others to get close,
then the female owner
might be pregnant,
Four,
if your cat keeps scratching
at the door or make
unusual noises to wake you up
at night, but it's
not their usual behavior.
You should check
for gas leaks or intruders.
It's very likely that they
have sensed something
and are trying to alert you.
Five,
if your cat becomes
much more attached to you
and more frequently rubs
against furniture or corners.
The cat makes sense that it's
near the end of its life
by leaving it sent on you
in the surrounding.
Your cat wants to tell
other cats that you are a human
with the cat's protection
and should not be messed with.