Do you know how to spin a ball on your feet?
So I can do a lot of things in the basketball.
A lot of things which are ain't really my thing.
I bet you anything.
Drew said, he didn't think you knew how well drew.
You don't be better than that.
You think all of your teammates for usab can do it.
That is the one thing that I cannot do as a little kid.
Don't you just sit here and practice this all day?
I can give you like 1/2 a second,
maybe1,000 really at the point guard.
I don't know how to do Terry's.
All right.
Jin Zi, I heard you can bounce it off your knee.
It's about to that's good.
Should someone be able to know how to do this if they play basketball?
No, you don't have too good.
Do you know how to spin a ball on your finger?
No.
I'll be the only guy on the team.