We should start making
breakups not relationships,
the trend.
It's clear
how much they
negatively affect
our emotions,
mental health,
and even our bodies,
even people who
aren't religious
are now constantly talking
about the harm.
These relationships calls
a forbidden relationship
is nothing but regret
our social circles.
Tv shows and movies
have normalized this
so much that we
can't even see
the damage it's doing
in TV shows
the characters
are with someone new
Every episode
going through all sorts
of experiences,
and we are seeing
this more and more
in real life, too.
Please, let's not get caught up
in these normalized ugliness.
Relationships
shouldn't be taking so lightly.
They should have
value and meaning.
You might say we love
each other so much.
I can't leave,
but here we
need to weigh
the costs and benefits.
I'd rather endure
the pain of a breakup
than poison both
of my worldly life
and my afterlife
by engaging
in a forbidden relationship,
the pain.