I gave my ants
a Twinkie and little
Did I know that this
would lead
to a battle
of the species?
I embedded
the Twinkie
near the ants nest.
and they swarmed
all over it,
even toppling
the Twinkie
to the ants.
The Twinkie was
righteous grub
and they
picked away at it,
taking it piece
by piece
down to their nest.
But after a while,
something unexpected happened,
they were staying
away from the Twinkies.
This made no sense
until I took
a closer look.
I could see
a different species
of small red ants
had taken
over the remnants
of the Twinkies.
As the big ants
tried to approach
the delicacy,
the short kings
fought them off,
or should I say
short queens?
The way
the little ants
do this is they
would latch
onto the antennaes and legs
of the larger ants
scaring them off.
Later that night,
something unexpected happened,
a security camera
caught this have
Alina scarfing
down the Twinkie ants
and all.