Uh Live is all good, sir.
Excellent work.
Here's your oxygen
where to boss
just down there
and keep on going for this one.
Any particular destination?
just write down.
I kind of need to know the...
just down
just write down
yeah but what...
Down there?
look, we're sending everyone.
It's all hands on deck,
it's 7 o'clock in the morning.
I'm just following orders.
He hasn't even got anyone with him.
yeah It's another false start I'm afraid.
what do we all need to go?
I've got orders to send everyone
well who's going to look after the brain
not important right now.
Honestly,
these apes.
come on,
you better get going,
It's just embarrassing.
You're a braver cell than me!
Poor guy
out of my way!
I'm late!