does Lucky help you film?!
No, he doesn't.
I'm very specific with how
I want my angles
and how I wante to shot
and how I want it to look.
So he's offered.
I've just politely declined.
How far in advance
do you plan your TikTok, recipes and videos?!!
that depends on what I'm doing
and what my current situation looks like.
Sometimes I'm traveling.
So I preplan some things and I
preshoot some stuff,
or I just kind of make it up the night
before and I'm like oh
that would be cool tomorrow.
Or a lot of the times I
film what I would naturally do already,
like my meal prep videos
I would naturally meal prep.
And anyway, so I just film that
or making different dinners
or making my kids things
that they requested,
because they actually do request
those things.
so yeah It depends.
It's a mix of things.