IPhone 16
and IPhone 16 PRO are
helpful when it
comes to things
like writing,
expressing
yourself
visually and getting
everyday things
done with Siri.
oh I do
everyday things
like all the time,
but apple Intelligence.
You get writing
tools that help
you summarize,
rewrite and proofread.
Plus,
they can help you
change your tone
to sound more professional,
concise,
or friendly.
okay But I
don't want
this thing
trying to do
in my writing
for me.
All the writing
is still up
to you.
But now it
quickly correct
spelling
grammar
and finishes
in Complete
sentences.
Good,
cause my words are
like my children,
my misspelled
dramatically incorrect children,
no judgment.