My best friend unexpectedly lost her dad almost 6 years ago.
And for her wedding,
I knew I wanted to somehow surprise her with a keepsake with her dad's remains
and I decided on a bouquet charm,
so he could still walk her down the aisle.
I've never before worked with the committed remains of someone I personally knew
while they were alive and i've never created a memorial this tiny.
So this project was a huge deal for me.
I went to her mom for her permission first
and she thought it was such a great idea
and really wanted me to go through with it.
I first put some of his remains into a small pendant,
and then I used her wedding colors to create a pearly marble design on top.
And then I added a picture of them into the little keepsake box
her mom and I decided to give the charm to her
at the end of her rehearsal dinner with her fiance and brother there as well.
and She loved it and kept it with her throughout her wedding the next day.
This was such an important piece to me.
So let me know what you think in the comments.