Come shopping with me
at Ralph Lauren.
Obviously,
I was spoiled for choice,
but it had to narrow it down.
okay So this looked
beautiful off the hunger.
But actually on,
I don't think it
really flattered me.
The material was
gorgeous, obviously,
but I don't think
it was very ..... WOW.
But this,
on the other hand,
this doesn't even do it Justice.
The colors
are so vibrant and beautiful.
I would need a tailored,
but it just looks so expensive.
okay So this was a flop.
It was way too revealing,
in my opinion.
And I just didn't know
how to tie the front.
Again... I love the gorgeous
colors of this.
I feel like it flatters,
my skin tone really well.
But the actual court
not that flattering.
Let me know in the comments
which one is your favorite.
I have really been loving these
rich vibrant colors recently.
I'm obsessed.