First day in Germany.
Why is the supermarket closed?
What?
shops are closed on Sundays?
Why?
That's crazy.
1 week in Germany
oh No,
it's Sunday again.
oh I don't have anything left to eat.
How am I gonna eat groceries now?
1 month in Germany
oh crap.
Tomorrow is Sunday again,
I gotta go get some food,
oh half an hour until the supermarket closes
1 year in Germany.
Sundays are so peaceful without the hassle of shopping.
Kind of nice.
Why don't more countries have this?
10 years in Germany
I can't imagine Sundays any other way.
It's perfect.
Everybody is at home, has time to meet friends.
hey Honey,
can you help me carry those boxes to the basement?
Are you crazy?
Sunday is "Ruhetag"
nothing is to be worked