Are you sureyou're not Jamaican?
Yes I am sure
Well, you look just likethe girl whocleans my house
Bring me a cup of chamomile tea
Will you, dear?
Oh I will let your server know ma'am
Once we get your lab results back
Who is that?
Dr. Chol?
I want him.
Excuse me?
Oh no offense, dear
The orientals make the best doctors
It's their math skills
Biopsy's back on Gertrude
Lymphoma?
Not cancer
Non-caseating granulomas
That's good news
I'm waiting for one more test to come back
and if the results are what I think they are,
I'd like to deliver the news
Hi, Mrs Kovacc.
We have some news for you
Yeah?
Sarcoidosis
What's that?
It's very treatable
Does Dr. Chol agree?
Absolutely
What am I looking at?
The graph of your genetic makeup
You're part of African-American
What?
Come on, sister
Put it here
Give it here
we got to stick together