It's okay,
come and see see
this yellow dot.
Let's press it
gently with the key.
You can see that I
can easily shift gears
without stepping
on the brake.
In fact,
your car has a lot
of emergency functions
today I will tell you
all you can like it, save it.
First,
our car key
is locked
in the car,
then the car door
can't be opened,
don't panic
at this time.
Let me find a roll
of tape,
stick it on the glass.
The tape is already stuck
next, we pull
the glass down hard.
See the glass is lowered,
take out the key
to unlock it.
The car door will open.
Second,
we are driving
on the road.
If the brakes suddenly fail,
don't panic,
we just need to hold
the electronic hand brake
and hold it,
then the vehicle can stop steadily.
Finally,
we are trapped in the car
and can't get out.
We fold
down the rear seats
and climb into the trunk.
Then find this mechanism
on the trunk door panel,
just push
the trunk and it
will open.
Have you learned it?
Follow me to learn
some car knowledge
every day?