travel the world with a camera and all my friends
and I'm gonna show you guys
what 2023 looked like for me
in January I took a flight to Belize
and backpacked through the coastal islands
before making my way into Guatemala
this is where I crossed something off my bucket list
of climbing an active volcano
jumping off rope swings into
crocodile infested waters and exploring ancient cities
I then flew to Japan almost immediately after
on a 200 dollar one way ticket
I was lucky enough to see
Mount Fuji for three days straight while I was there
after a few weeks
my buddy and I hopped on another
one way flight to Chang Mai Thailand
upon arriving
we met a couple of Swedish guys in our hostel
and after just one night of hanging out
we decided to travel together
for the coming weeks
our friend group grew to almost 15
people when we were all traveling together
Thailand was stunning
but it was time to get back to the United States for an American summer
I spent four weeks
traveling up the California coast with my buddy Caleb
before meeting up with the rest of the
crew in Southern Oregon
on one of our first days together
a
blizzard struck and we decided to play a baseball game
for two months straight we did new things every day
hiking to the tops of mountains
setting up trampolines on docks and piers
and even rollerblading
through America's most pristine mountains
fall came quicker than ever
and we were on to our next mission
we all flew to Peru
and for four weeks
we saw some of the country's most incredible sights
and explored one of the seven wonders of the world
then we got the sudden urge to go to Costa Rica
I ate more tacos than I could imagine
and I got sick