You have a problem? Yes, I do.
I've had a long day.
Is it too much to ask for a dinner with a little peace and quiet?
Sheldon, you do not talk to your father like that.
Fine.
I'd rather not speak to any of you.
I got this.
George, maybe you should calm down.
First.
I got this.
You want to explain yourself.
I'd rather just go to bed since I have to be up in a few hours.
Anyway.
I understand you're tired, but that is no reason.
I'm not just tired.
I'm exhausted.
Everything hurts.
I get up in the morning to do this job I don't even like,
and I'm doing it just for the money,
and it's not even a lot of money.
I keep trying harder and harder,
and it doesn't even make a difference?
So you're going to yell at me or punish me.
Let's just get it over with.
I won't punish you.
Why not?
I deserve it
Let me tell you about my day.
I got yelled at by the principal for benching a linebacker who was flunking English.
Then I got yelled at even more by the kid's parents. Then I had to break up the fight in the locker room, got elbowed in the neck.
That's a rough day.
It was all before 10:00 am. So I get what you're going through.
But you notice, I didn't come home and take it out on you.
No, you didn't.
I want you get back in there.
Apologize to everyone,
and finish your dinner, sir.