A wolf is a big wild dog roaming around in the landscape
just trying to feed itself and raise young.
A wolf represents or symbolizes the wild to many people.
They take on a very romantic,
glorified sort of appearance.
They're killers.
That's what they put on this earth for, was to kill,
and they're indiscriminate killers.
To me,
the wolf is a teacher challenging us to think beyond the limitations
of our current perspectives regarding a lot of things.
Makes hair stand up in the back of my neck.
When I see one,
I'II guess I feel what all these other animals feel their eyes look
through you.
That's very unsettling to people.
They're all business,
they're afraid of nothing and they're not gonna change.
If you want to make them change,
they say kill me.
I ain't gonna change, though.
That's a wolf.