The trauma
The post traumatic stress of my last performance on the "Jimmy Fallon show"
Last time you were on the show
This is… This is late night
We just had met
We've never met each other
And you couldn't be nicer and sweeter
And, gosh,  I'm a fan of yours
And you…you came out and…and you sat just the way you're sitting
Very nice and we were talking
And I just gave you a compliment and then you said:
Before you continue…
(Before you) even start the interview…
(yeah) I just dove straight in there with…
I love that Halloween candy thing that you do
And…and I said
And there was just silence
I said the Halloween candy thing. Is that right?
And you're like, "the candy corn thing?"
Yeah I thought it…
No
You go, "when you get kids, you trick them."
I go, "That's Jimmy Kimmel. "