What's really interesting
with apple devices is
there's this little ring
around the charging port.
And if you remove
that ring,
well ....
it actually gives you
the perfect amount
of space
for USB-C port.
Not sure if that's something apple
did intentionally,
but Ken
seems to be having
a field day
with the fact
that they did that.
Now we
have to unscrew
the actual cup,
and well you think
you just unscrew,
but no,
that's not the case.
So this screw you
unscrew properly.
Lefty loosy.
Righty Tighty.
Nice.
That's all good to go.
And this screw,
you actually unscrew
the right way,
like actually right way,
clockwise, nice.
And the same goes
for this screw.
You unscrew it clockwise,
and then this screw
counterclockwise.
so The thing
about this mod is
you can't really find
these charging port
replacements online.
So.. you can actually use
ken's replacement part
as a replacement part.
And you'll
also get the upgrade
to USB-C which
is pretty awesome.
We need more people
like Ken in this world.