Come and spend
a day with me.
So we have a fun day planned.
I started off shopping,
I had a browse around Ralph,
and there were a few dresses I
want to try.
And I also needs to get
some trousers tailored
whilst I was there.
This is option one.
I thought it was cute,
but it is giving milkmaid.
So I decided not,
but the shoes,
on the other hand,
are just divine.
So obviously I
picked those up.
After that strenuous activity,
I needed a Starbucks,
white chocolate mocha.
Thank me later.
We headed to Harrods
and just browsed
at the jewelry.
And the chocolate hall
is literally my favorite
place ever.
After a day
of morning shopping,
I really wants to go
to the gym,
so I had to third space
and went for a quick dip
in the pool.
This is literally my new
favorite thing to do.
But I had to rush
home and jump
on the train
to Cambridge
because I
was planning to meet
my best friends.
How cute sit here by the way.
And here's Laura,
she's so adorable.
We headed
to the Shakespeare festival
to see
our best friend form pepper
and she was insane,
it was so wholesome.