You'll never guess which
of these two puppets
is real and which is fake.
As the show starts,
workers push two connected puppets
onto the stage.
When they land. The man bends
his body in a crazy way.
Like he has no bones
and even lifts one leg.
Judges and audience are shocked
trying to figure out who is real.
The man then stands up slowly,
and the woman lifts him,
he bends even more,
almost touching his head to his feet.
Some people think the man
must be fake, but they're wrong.
The man picks up the woman
and spins her like a music box figurine.
When the woman lifts the man.
He dances with his legs
in the air,
but then the man
lifts the woman again,
and the judges see her legs
have vanished,
leaving just her shoes.
They wonder if she is fake,
suddenly the man spins
and another man appears
from under her skirt,
he was controlling both puppets.
The judges are amazed.