Meeting someone online can feel strange at first.
It's our natural instinct to shy away
but after seeing that person on screen day after day,
that person suddenly feels familiar and a day without them feels..
like something is missing
The relationship may deep into the point
where someone is ready to say,
I love you.
But technology can only take a relationship so far.
At some point, the only way for growth is to take the leap and actually meet in person.
Are you ready to finally see Mira in person?
And nothing beats that unforgettable moment
when you realize you've been cat fished,
what happened today you completely ignored Mira.
I thougt Mira was a cat.
You thought Mira was a cat.