Be brave and make a secret gaming base under the bed.
Oliver's small bedroom had a regular layout
just a bed and wardrobe with no privacy
as a game lover,
He often got scolded by his mom,
and there wasn't even room for a desk
after getting fed up
He decided to kick everything out and start fresh.
He welded a stepped bed frame against the wall
using galvanized square steel,
covered it with eco-friendly wood veneers
and added a big, comfy mattress
to make it bump proof.
He added soft cushions on the sides.
Under the bed,
Oliver created a large corner wardrobe
to hang his stylish clothes
and store out of season bedding
with pull out baskets for shorts, pants, and socks.
A gauze curtain made it feel like a private dressing room
for safety, he added an iron guard rail
and a movable bookcase next to the bed
which connected to a suspended desk by the window,
forming a study area with a small blackboard for planning.
the coolest part behind the bookcase was a secret gaming base with a computer desk
a full set of e-sports gear and even a mini fridge under the desk,
he also added a perforated board for displaying his high end gaming equipment.
Now Oliver can enjoy his gaming world without worrying about his mom catching him.