While number ten,
Downing Street might see a new prime minister move
in after the UK elections this week
There's one resident who isn't going anywhere.
Larry,
the cat known officially as chief mouser to the Cabinet Office has been
in number ten for more than a decade
overseeing the departure of four prime ministers.
The tabby cat was a rescue adopted by then prime Minister David Cameron
in 2011 to solve the building's rat crisis.
His day to day activities at the pm's official residents are:
according to the government,
greeting guests,
inspecting security defenses and testing antique furniture for napping quality.
While he's seen prime ministers come and go,
he's also ignored plenty of famous faces as they visited his abode,
including former President Donald Trump,
and ahead of a visit by President Joe Biden to Downing Street in 2023.
Larry was removed from his favorite spot by a member of the Downing Street team.
Larry's resilience and diligence in his role has earned him a place
in the hearts of the nation as Britain's favorite mog
and top cat of this most famous street.