I made my cat a gym because
he's been putting on a little weight.
So I cleared out this room
other than the trampoline,
because that is going to service
his practice Boxing ring.
I then moved in his exercise wheel,
a treadmill,
a scratching post for working on his climbing,
a yoga mat for stretching,
a bench and a dumbbell,
and then a speed training section.
It was coming along nicely,
but the final touch needed
was some mirrors.
And then after he checked it out for a bit,
it was time to get a workout in.
So he started with stretching,
and he got straight on the exercise wheel.
He needed a little help,
but he did great,
and he was feeling himself afterwards.
Then he did some grip strength,
training.
yes Sir,
good,
hold it ... hold it,
good good oh oh good form.
He didn't really know how the treadmill worked,
but that's okay.
You ready?
14, not bad.
Great first day, buddy.
Good