What a brilliant idea.
So we can tow it.
of course Very sturdy.
Let's go.
hey Stop it,
hey bro,
this will damage the car.
Where's the tow hook?
I've never bought
a tow hitch.
All cars have it.
Come on, let's open the trunk.
Under this cover.
There is a set of portable tools.
look This is the toe hook.
There is a small cover on
the front of the car.
Look, that's it.
We can take it off
by pressing it
with our hands,
then plug in the toe hook,
tighten it counterclockwise,
umfold the toe rope in half and
thread it through the toe hook.
The long end is the main rope.
The short end is an auxiliary rope.
Take the main rope
out of the rope,
then tighten,
wrap the auxiliary rope
around the main rope
for 1 week,
hold it in half and thread it
through the loop above,
then tighten the main row.
This method is also known
as rage to death cow
because even ten cows
can't break the rope.
It's also very easy to untie.
We just need to grab
this auxiliary row,
then pull it.
Look, the trailer knot is untied.
It's really simple,
right?
Follow me to make
a friend who knows cars.