okay I just learned
the great live hack if you see
something that you
wanna take a picture of,
but you left your phone at home,
don't worry, just do this,
blindfold yourself for like 30 minutes
and then stare at what you
wanna take a picture of for
3 minutes. Next,
pull out one of your eyeballs
and cut it in half top to bottom.
Throw the back half
into a 14% potassic alum solution.
Within 24 hours,
the rhodopsin on your retina
will become fixed
into a permanent image
of the last thing
you were looking at.
It's called an optogram
and no one's ever done it.
At least not to themselves.
The process was invented
in the late 1800s.
Here's an optogram from the retina
of a rabbit that
was forced to stare
at a window.
Now, at the turn of the century,
this caused a lot of excitement
optograms might help us
solve crimes, right?
We could look at the eyes
of victims and see
the last thing they saw.
Unfortunately, optograms are
a very poor quality.
Here's one from the retina
of a rabbit that looked
at a picture of Salvador Dali.
Their poor quality
means they have
no forensic value.
So keep your eyes
in their sockets.