A big misconception
about blindness
is that everyone
who is blind
sees like this.
In reality,
blindness is a spectrum
and only a small percentage
see nothing at all,
tends to be more like these
visual impairment examples.
First one, here is diabetic retinopathy,
which affects about 9.6 million people
in the United States
Next up here, we have an example
of a severe form of cataracts.
It affects about 20 million people
in the United States
but is highly treatable.
Next up here, we have glaucoma,
which affects about 3 million americans,
and is the second leading cause
of blindness worldwide.
Next up here,
we have macular degeneration,
which affects about 20 million people
in the United States
Next up here is
an example of what it might be
like for somebody who can only see
lights and shadows
and not much else.