When the woman woke up,
she found an owl perched
on her windowsill,
holding a letter in its beak,
reminiscent of a magical scene
from Harry Potter
However, when the woman
tried to take the letter,
the owl refused to let go.
so She turned around and went
inside to get a toy mouse,
attempting to trade with the owl,
but it still wouldn't release the letter.
Finally, after trying another toy,
when she attempted to take the letter again,
the owl finally relented.
As a token of gratitude,
the woman decided to give
the toy to the owl.
In fact, this owl would visit
the woman's windowsill every day.
Her cat curious about the visitor likely mistook
it for a monster. When the owl
turned its head, the cat
was so frightened that it ran away,
looking quite comical.
The owl itself seemed
quite puzzled by the whole ordeal.
The reason the owl visited
the window every day was that the woman
had once saved it when it was young.
Therefore, it would come
to visit her, perhaps as a way
to express gratitude.