One day,
Einstein
was sitting
next to an Indian man
on a flight.
Einstein says ... you know
it's a long flight.
Why don't we have a competition?
I'll ask you a question.
And if you can't answer it,
you will give me $5.
Then you can ask me a question.
and If I can't answer it,
i'll pay you $500.
The Indian man
thought this was
a great deal.
He told Einstein .... all right
You go first.
Einstein asks, how far is
the moon from the earth?
The Indian man said,
I don't know the exact answer.
Here's $5.
He then looked at Einstein
and asked what
goes up a hill
with three legs
and comes down with four.
Einstein worked through all
of his knowledge of science,
but couldn't figure it out.
so He put his hand
into his pocket
and gave him $500.
Now, it's Einstein's turn again.
Einstein said,
before I ask you my next question,
what does go up the hill
with three legs and come
down with four?
The Indian man put his hand
into his pocket
and gave him $5.