Hear the whole idea about like the chosen people
or the chosen people
or the chosen people.
okay Fine.
You think you're chosen people,
good for you.
Everybody think they're chosen,
Christians think they're chosen,
Muslim,
think they're chosen.
This is like me coming into your broadcast studios,
like hey my fortune cookie told me that this is mine.
Now.
and I'm allowed to kill you.
What drives increases.
The Christian Zionist Jewish people are a cherished people.
They are a chosen people.
God chose those people,
isn't Jesus,
your guy?
Come you believe in a in a in a religion...
in a god and a doctrine?
But you believe that other people from another religion
are chosen over?
You?
Don't you feel un chosen?
Right?
I mean this is like a like a religious polygamy,
right?
Like are you are you cheating on Jesus?
Is this some sort of a religious formal?
What does it mean to be chosen?
Do you have a bottle service?
yeah Do you have like a VIP lounge axis?
Are you like in a waterfront condos?
And we were like back in the purgatory?