Welcome back to the series
where we saw things
the wrong way.
This item is
this really wacky
Halter top.
She looks like ..
how you're supposed to
wear it on.
We have it on
like a necklace,
have this chain
and I'm gonna slip it through.
And now it's kind
of like a strap
in the back.
Have this like halter top,
but it's backless,
it's still gonna add
on these trousers
can match the vibes
of the Top.
They were starting
in with the halter top.
I'm just putting
it on backwards
to see if it works
is giving modern elegance.
So I think we're
gonna have to go
with some gold jewelry.
me and my boyfriend yesterday
we're actually thinking
about going to New York
for just a day ..
literally just a day.
We didn't get
a little New York breeze
up our sleeve
you know what I mean.
And now we're gonna go
in for the shoes.
It's probably way too cold
outside where you
live to just go
bare arm like this.
And then for bag,
yeah this outfit
is just too good.
And as always.