I'm going
to a Christian concert
and I don't know
what to wear.
I'm seeing Forrest Frank and
Josiah Queen two of my
favorite Christian artists
help me choose
an outfit
option One is comfy and cutesy
with the pleaded skirt,
oversized, chronic
and pastel color palette.
I absolutely love
the graphics on a sweatshirt.
Sticking with the pastel theme
for Alpha two,
the concert is part of
"the child of god" tour.
So I thought the overalls were
super fitting, leaning
into my inner kid.
For option three.
I'm rocking unit hard robber
with another oversized sweatshirt
for a super chill Look,
this fit is so comfy,
perfect for dancing,
praising all night, long,
1 .. 2 .. or 3, which one
should I wear tonight?!!
Bye.