All right, here's a story.
Many of you might be seeing your news feeds today.
Disney just announced a whole lot of new attractions coming
to both Disney World and Disneyland
So there's a lot to talk about and we're just barely scratching the surface here.
So let's start in Orlando.
Magic kingdom is getting a brand new land based on Disney villains.
We're told it'll have two major attractions along with dining and shopping.
Hollywood studios is getting a monsters inc land.
We're told it will include the first suspended roller coaster ever at a Disney park.
I predict you will be on that.
I would try that one look at this in California.
The avengers campus at Disneyland is gonna double in size thanks to two new attractions.
They're called stark flight lab
and the previously announced avengers infinity defense animal kingdom
getting a new encanto and Indiana Jones attractions.
And finally a new avatar land is coming to California adventure.
Opening dates for most of those new attractions by the way have yet to be released.