This guy
just threw
a paper airplane
in the football stadium
while a match
was being played,
and you won't believe
what happened.
So he gets ready to make
the best paper airplane throw
of his life.
As you can see,
it kept going straight forward.
But something amazing
is about to happen.
You see, the people around him
started to realize that the plane
wasn't going to stop
and that it
could actually reach the field.
But that's not the best part.
Just watch what's about to happen.
I wonder if any of the players
saw this happening,
although they were
probably more focused on the game.
But as the plane gets closer,
you can see that it starts turning,
and the plane is actually going
straight for the goal.
If you think this guy just made
the best paper airplane throw
of his life,
consider subscribing.