For the love of god,
don't do these things.
When you come to Japan,
there are so many things
you don't want to do on the train.
But one thing no one talks about
is the sneaky out of service train.
If no one gets on it, when it stops,
so everybody gets off
suddenly then don't make the mistake.
I've made so many times
and just follow the crowd.
Then when it's time to get on,
put your backpack in the front,
when it's crowded,
get your spot and be quiet,
or if you don't want to rawdog,
the train ride get your earphones ready.
Also don't use the train
like a jungle gym.
I've seen tourists use these
like monkey bars,
and If that's too complicated,
then you can get a taxi,
but don't miss open taxis
because the colors are reversed.
Green means taken
and red means available.
Also don't ignore the colors
on vending machines.
The blue ones are called drinks,
and red ones are hot drinks.
These can be really useful as hand warmers
in the winter and cooling packs
in the summer,
which the heat and humidity in Japan,
June through September is so bad.
All I have to say is do not come
instead come with us in October.
When we're hosting a group tour,
we're going to Kyoto, Osaka,
and even to feed
the deer in Nara,
there are still spots open now.