I want to know
how you eat
a cupcake,
because I hear you eat
one differently.
And I want to learn
Obi-Wan.
ok So I didn't realize
that this was that
unusual Intelligence.
My friend Steph's,
40th birthday,
okay
and it got Omicron.
So we couldn't have
a cake.
So we did a cupcakes.
I got Omicron
I got Omicron.
and uh so I took
my cupcake,
and I was sat there,
and we were having
a conversation,
and I did this thing,
and it stopped the party.
Now I have stopped
parties before,
but never for a good reason.
And this was
a good way
to stop a party.
So you take the Top.
oh
and you pull it apart,
and then you flip it.
oh
You like ...
like a whoopie pie,
almost like you
make it to ..
and then you have
a sandwich,
and you don't get
frosting up your nose.
um um