you know
how you know
When you're driving
the wrong cars,
if I ask you
what car you
drive and you
tell me
the derivative,
not the brand.
So if I said,
what do you drive?
So I drive GT86.
You don't tell me
I drive a Toyota coop,
ok
right?!!
Because the person
drives an Aston Martin
doesn't go out drive DV9
yeah
or vanquish.
they asked,
what do I drive?
I drive an Aston Martin,
I drive a Bentley.
Do you get
enough like a Bentley?
yeah I don't need to tell
you if it's a Mulsanne
or if it's continental or
it's a Bentley.
Now,
the problem
with Toyota was
they were making
their cars in Japan,
exporting them
to America
for the American person.
It was still a Toyota,
it represented
reliability and quality,
but it
didn't quite represent
opulance
and luxury.
And one day
they're having
a conversation
about what are we
gonna do
with this problem.
And they thought
the problem
was about pricing
out of nowhere a little voice
from the back
said this is
not a pricing problem.
It's a brand problem.
So we
should just rather than change
the car,
just change the logo
on the car.
And then what we call it?
And the answer was
it's a luxury product.
What do we do?
We export it
to the US it's
a luxury export to the US
Lexus.
It's a Lexus.