Ryan wake up,
school is not a place to sleep,
well then home is not a place to study.
Jonathan,
stop eating in my class.
Dude, didn't you have breakfast this morning?
No,
but I didn't have time for my second breakfast,
Jonathan,
first eating then talking
not talking while you're eating.
Since you've got so much to say,
name ten elements on the periodic table.
Second breakfast can I just say that of all the idiots,
in all the idiot villages,
in all the idiot worlds,
you stand alone, my friend,
fine, I'll come write it on the board
if you don't believe me.
Second breakfast.
He is officially the smartest kid in the world.
His mind is greater than all of ours.
Combined.
His brain power transcends time and space.
Shall we tell him?
Absolutely not.
It's not impossible.
Sometimes my genius is,
it's almost frightening.