Watch,
as this professor explains,
life's most important philosophy.
The ending is
truly eye opening.
Is this jar full?
yes
Is it full now?
Yes
and How about now?
Is the jar full now?
Yes.
now I want you to recognize
this jar represents your life,
golf balls.
It is important things,
your family,
your friends,
your health,
and your passions.
The pebbles are
the other important things
Your job,
your home,
the sand is
everything else
it's just a small stuff.
Now,
if you put the sand in the jar first,
you won't have room
for the pebbles
of the golf course.
The same is true in life.
You spend all your energy
and your time
on the small stuff
You won't have time
for all the really important things
that matter to you.