you complain about a life that you chose
you are not a victim
not at all
your generosity concealed something dirtier and meaner
you're incapable of facing your ambitions
and you resent me for it
but I'm not the one who put you where you are
I have nothing to do with it
you're not sacrificing yourself as you say
you
choose to sit on the sidelines because you're afraid
because your pride makes your head
explode before you can even come up with a little
germ of an idea
and now you wake up
and your 40 and you need someone to blame
and you're the one to blame
you're petrified by your own fucking standards
and your fear of failure
this is the truth